Please provide us your email, so we can sent you a login code. Then click the Send Code button.
scene 02  enter-the-code
raw        7.08s on camera
scene      00:00:06.800 to 00:00:13.900  (7.1s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 19 words, 5.5s     beats 0.3s     exit 0.8s
scene-02-enter-the-code
We sent you a four-digit code to that address.  If you are not seeing it, check your spam folder.
scene 03  dashboard
raw        6.52s on camera
scene      00:00:13.900 to 00:00:20.400  (6.5s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 16 words, 4.7s     beats 0.5s     exit 0.8s
scene-03-dashboard
This is your dashboard.  You can return here anytime with the command + K short keys.
scene 04  find-the-business
raw        8.52s on camera
scene      00:00:20.400 to 00:00:25.500  (5.1s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 13 words, 3.8s     exit 0.8s
scene-04-find-the-business
Type the name of a business, then select it from the dropdown list.
scene 05  the-business
raw        5.72s on camera
scene      00:00:25.500 to 00:00:31.200  (5.7s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 14 words, 4.1s     beats 0.3s     exit 0.8s
scene-05-the-business
This is the business info page.  Click the lookup icon to find the stores.
scene 06  find-the-store
raw        9.52s on camera
scene      00:00:31.200 to 00:00:36.000  (4.8s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 11 words, 3.2s     beats 0.3s     exit 0.8s
scene-06-find-the-store
Type the store name,  then select it from the dropdown list.
scene 07  the-store
raw        7.92s on camera
scene      00:00:36.000 to 00:00:42.000  (6.0s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 15 words, 4.4s     beats 0.3s     exit 0.8s
scene-07-the-store
Now you are on the store details page.  Click the gear, then choose Lookup Items.
scene 08  item-list
raw        6.0s on camera
scene      00:00:42.000 to 00:00:48.000  (6.0s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 14 words, 4.1s     beats 0.6s     exit 0.8s
scene-08-item-list
This is the lookup items search.  To add new item,  click the plus button.
scene 09  new-item
raw        18.96s on camera
scene      00:00:48.000 to 00:00:54.000  (6.0s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 16 words, 4.7s     exit 0.8s
scene-09-new-item
Give the item a name. Then choose the collection it belongs to, and create this item.
scene 10  item-details
raw        35.88s on camera
scene      00:00:54.000 to 00:01:26.600  (32.6s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 32 words, 9.3s     beats 22.0s     exit 0.8s
scene-10-item-details
Now add the item details. Add an image first.  Then add a description,  Add the quantity.  And the price.  Select the requirement.  Then select the boot size as a variant  and save.
scene 11  saved
raw        4.2s on camera
scene      00:01:26.600 to 00:01:30.800  (4.2s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 10 words, 2.9s     exit 0.8s
scene-11-saved
That is the item ready for the store to rent.
scene 12  back-to-dashboard
raw        5.4s on camera
scene      00:01:30.800 to 00:01:36.200  (5.4s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 14 words, 4.1s     exit 0.8s
scene-12-back-to-dashboard
Back to the dashboard where you can log out or select a card option.
scene 13  sign-out
raw        5.2s on camera
scene      00:01:36.200 to 00:01:39.000  (2.8s)
lead-in    0.5s     speech 5 words, 1.5s     exit 0.8s
scene-13-sign-out
You are now logged out.